World War III.
（岡部倫太郎(おかべりんたろう)）第３次世界大戦…
By 2036,
（阿万音鈴羽(あまねすずは)）
その結果 2036年には―
it will have resulted in 5.7 billion casualties worldwide.
世界中の57億人が
犠牲になっている
And this is what starts it.
きっかけは これ
Huh? What is it?
（椎名(しいな)まゆり）これ？ 何だろう
It's only a model.
（橋田 至(はしだいたる)）ロボじゃね？
変形とかしたりして
Maybe it transforms or something?
A time machine.
（岡部）タイムマシンだ
（まゆり）えっ？
Seriously?
（橋田）マジ？
I knew you'd recognize it, Uncle.
（鈴羽）さすが おじさん
知ってるんだね
Then that makes this easy.
だったら 話は早い
Come with me.
私と一緒に来て
（岡部）断る
I refuse.
（鈴羽）あっ
（橋田）えっ？
Okarin?
オカリン？
I came here from the alpha world line.
（岡部）
俺はアルファ世界線から
ここへ来た
Over the past three weeks,
この３週間 何度も何度も
世界線を変え―
I changed the world line again and again,
sacrificing Kurisu to return to the beta world line.
紅莉栖(くりす)を犠牲にして―
このベータ世界線に
たどり着いたんだ
I won't let it all be for naught!
そのすべてをムダにするなんて
そんなことはできない
Kurisu?
紅莉栖さん？
紅莉栖…
Kurisu?
あっ たしかこの前―
Wasn't that the name of the scientist
ラジ館で刺された科学者が
そんな名前だったんじゃね？
who was stabbed at the radio building?
Okabe Rintarou,
岡部倫太郎
what if I told you that the way to avoid World War III
もしも 世界大戦を回避するのに
必要なことが―
is, on July 28th, 2010,
2010年７月28日に亡くなった―
to prevent Makise Kurisu's death?
牧瀬(まきせ)紅莉栖を助けることだと
言ったら？
What do you mean?
（岡部）どういうことだ？
I don't know the details,
詳しいことは分からない
but I have one mission:
ただ 私が受けた
ミッションは１つ
To save Makise Kurisu
牧瀬紅莉栖を救い―
and to go to the one world line unaffected by the attractor field,
アトラクタフィールドの
干渉を受けない―
唯一の世界線…
the Steins Gate!
シュタインズ･ゲートを目指せ
Open the
Steins Gate
Steins Gate?
（岡部）シュタインズ… ゲート
～
The architects of this plan were
（鈴羽）この計画を立てたのは
未来のおじさんと 父さん
my father and your future self.
None of it is anything more than a hypothesis.
すべては推測でしかない
It's possible the theory is wrong,
もしかしたら２人の理論は
間違っていて―
and there is no Steins Gate world line,
シュタインズ･ゲートなんて
世界線は存在しないのかもしれない
but I'm going anyway.
でも それでも 私は行く
I'll bet on the chance that a bright future's waiting for me.
すばらしい未来が待っているという
未知の可能性にかける
If you're coming with me,
もし おじさんが私と一緒に
行ってくれるなら―
then take my hand.
この手を握って
Um,
（まゆり）あのね…
Mayushii didn't really understand any of that,
まゆしぃは 今の話
チンプンカンプンなのです
but if this person,
でも その人が 紅莉栖さんって人が
オカリンにとって大切な人なら…
this Kurisu, is important to you,
shouldn't you try to help her?
頑張るべきじゃないかな
World War III sounds like one of your crazy fantasies.
（橋田）第３次世界大戦とか
オカリンの妄想に近すぎで―
No one else could handle it.
ほかに対応できる人間は
いないと思われ…
I don't care about the 5.7 billion people in the future...
（岡部）未来の57億人には
興味はない ただ…
but...
Thank you.
（鈴羽）ありがとう
（橋田･まゆり）エヘヘ…
Let's go.
すぐ乗って
Two people can get in it?
（岡部）２人 乗れるのか？
Of course!
（鈴羽）
もちろん 私の父さんが作った
最高傑作なんだから
This is my father's masterpiece.
（橋田）えっ ええ？
（まゆり）オカリン…
Okarin!
Leave your phone.
（鈴羽）携帯は置いていって
It might interfere with your phone in the past.
向こうのおじさんが持っている
携帯と 混線する可能性があるから
I'll be back.
（岡部）行ってくる
うん　頑張ってね
Good luck.
This is a time machine.
これがタイムマシン…
Yeah,
うん 1975年と2000年に
立ち寄ってきたけど―
I stopped in 1975 and 2000.
It's working fine,
状態は良好
but it's running out of fuel.
もっとも そろそろ
燃料がヤバイけどね
なっ？ 待て 過去から
未来にも行けるのか？
Wait. It can go from past to future?
当たり前じゃん
タイムマシンなんだから…
Of course it can.
It's a time machine.
I see.
（岡部）そうか あのときとは
世界線が違うから…
Is that because we're in a different world line now?
Sit down.
（鈴羽）座って
We'll head to just before noon on July 28th.
向かうのは７月28日の12時前
We can't change location,
到着する場所は変えられないから
あんまり前すぎると―
so if we arrive too early, it'll spread panic at the radio building,
ラジ館で騒ぎが起きて―
牧瀬紅莉栖の行動が
変わる可能性がある
possibly affecting Makise Kurisu's actions.
Your first time, the Gs are pretty tough.
初めてだと結構Ｇが
キツいから覚悟して
Get ready.
Okarin...
オカリン
What is this?
これは…
These always show up.
（鈴羽）必ず出るんだ
時のカケラみたいなもん
I guess they're like fragments of time.
Pretty, huh?
キレイでしょ
Let's go!
（鈴羽）行くよ
W-Wait.
（岡部）ま… 待て
胃液が逆流して
I think I'm going to throw up.
What a wimp.
（鈴羽）
もう だらしないなあ　急いで
Hurry!
Don't let your other self see you.
この時間にいる自分との
接触は避けて
It'll cause a serious time paradox.
深刻なタイムパラドックスが
起きるから
How long until her stabbing?
彼女が刺されるまで
どのくらい？
Twenty minutes or so, I guess.
あと 20分といったところか…
I'll prepare the time machine.
（鈴羽）私はタイムマシンの
セッティングしておくから―
You protect her, Uncle.
おじさんは彼女を守って
Stop calling me that.
（岡部）“おじさん”はやめろ
July 28th.
（岡部）７月28日…
On the day I saw Kurisu lying in a pool of blood,
血まみれで倒れていた
紅莉栖を見た あの日
I came with Mayuri to see
俺は まゆりと一緒に
中鉢(なかばち)博士の会見を見にきて―
Professor Nakabachi's press conference.
I heard a noise on the roof.
屋上の物音を聞いて
（岡部）ハッ！
あっ
That's right. After that, Mayuri went to the seventh-floor Upa machines.
（岡部）そういえば まゆりは
このあと ７階の うーぱの所に
マズい！
Oh, no!
You called me here for this?
（過去の岡部）お前
このために呼びつけたのか？
There aren't many left of this series, and Mayushii's...
（まゆり）このシリーズ
あまり残ってないのに―
まゆしぃは…
Oh well.
（岡部）しかたがない
奥の階段から８階へ戻るか
I'll take the back stairs to the eighth floor.
It's a metal... a metal Upa!
（まゆり）
メタルだよ メタルうーぱ
Is it rare?
（過去の岡部）レアなのか？
Really!
（まゆり）うん すっごく
Now that I'm here...
（岡部）ここまで来れば…
（岡部）ハッ？
（牧瀬紅莉栖）わっ すみませ…
I'm sorry.
K-Kurisu?
（岡部）く…
紅莉栖…
（紅莉栖）えっ？
H-How do you know my name?
どうして私の名前を？
Kurisu is alive.
（岡部）紅莉栖が… 生きている
Have we met somewhere?
どこかでお会いしましたっけ？
Kurisu...
（岡部）紅莉栖
Are you listening—
聞いてま… ハッ
何なんです？
What's wrong?
Answer me.
質問に答えてください
I...
俺は…
I... am...
俺は お前を…
（館内放送のチャイム）
Professor Nakabachi's press conference
（案内放送）
これより８階ホールにて
中鉢博士の会見が開かれます
will now begin in the eighth floor hall.
（岡部）くっ
（紅莉栖）あっ 待って
待ちなさい！
Wait!
（案内放送）
これより８階ホールにて…
（中鉢博士）えー 基本的な
タイムマシンの構造は―
In the handouts, you can read about the time machine's basic design.
配布した資料を
ご覧いただくとして―
Professor Nakabachi's Time Machine Invention Press Conference
I will use this conference as an opportunity to discuss the fundamental theory behind it.
ここでは 基礎的な理論のみ
解説していくことにする
The operation notes said that you'd be able to identify Makise Kurisu.
（鈴羽）計画書には
おじさんは 牧瀬紅莉栖を
マークできるはずだって
あったけど… できる？
Can you?
（岡部）ああ
Yeah.
（鈴羽）それと
Also, it's dangerous to take her outside.
彼女を外に連れだすのは
危険だから―
If we don't figure out who stabbed her,
殺害した者が誰なのか
原因を特定しないと―
we can't change her fate.
結局 死へと収束する可能性が高い
Just like Mayuri?
まゆりのときと同じか…
Doctor!
（過去の岡部）ドクター！
What is it?
（中鉢博士）なんだ いきなり
You know exactly what!
（過去の岡部）
“なんだ”ではない
What is this "time machine theory" of yours?
あなたの
タイムマシン理論は何だ！
Kerr Black Holes?
カーブラックホール 世界線
すべて ジョン･タイターの…
World lines?
You stole all of this from John Titor!
Kurisu will be stabbed right here soon.
（岡部）もうすぐ
紅莉栖は ここで…
Is she really going to be here?
本当に来るのか
Wait! Maybe she was stabbed elsewhere and brought here.
もしかして 別の場所で
刺されて ここに…
Yeah... That's possible!
そうか その可能性も…
（岡部）ハッ！ おっ…
Kurisu?
（岡部）紅莉栖…
So it does happen here.
やはり これからここで
What's she reading?
読んでいるのは―
A time machine?
タイムマシン…
Is that why she's the key to changing world lines?
だから 紅莉栖が世界線を
変える鍵に…
（男）ったく クソガキが
What do you want?
何の用だ
I wanted you to read this, Daddy.
あのね これを読んで欲しいの…
パパ
（岡部）パパ？
Daddy?
なっ！ 中鉢博士
Professor Nakabachi?
You contacted me for the first time in seven years.
パパが７年ぶりに連絡をくれて―
You asked me to come to your press conference, right?
会見を見に来いって
言ってくれたでしょ？
That was my inspiration.
それがきっかけになったの
Wait. So Kurisu's dad is...
（岡部）
まさか紅莉栖の父親が…
So I thought I could use it to theorize a time machine.
（紅莉栖）
もしかしたら タイムマシンが
作れるんじゃないかって…
I wanted to hear your ideas.
パパの意見を聞かせてほしいの
If this is accepted, you can use it
もし それが認められたら―
学会を追放された
パパのリベンジに…
as revenge for everyone who kicked you out—
I wasn't kicked out!
追放されたのではないっ！
I got sick of them and left.
私のほうが嫌気がさして
見切りをつけたのだ
Sorry.
（紅莉栖）ごめん
（中鉢博士）フン
It's not bad.
（中鉢博士）悪くない内容だ
Really?
（紅莉栖）ホント？ 私ね
パパさえよければ―
If you're okay with it,
I thought we could put both our names on the paper
それを共同署名で発表しても
いいと思ってるの
because you inspired me—
だって きっかけは パパが
Don't be stupid.
（中鉢博士）
バカなことを言うな！ 帰れ
Leave!
（紅莉栖）えっ？
I'll publish this paper under my name.
（中鉢博士）この論文は
私の名前で発表する
Wait!
（紅莉栖）そんな…
You wouldn't steal it, right, Daddy?
まさか パパ 盗むの？
I never thought you'd resort to tha—
そんなことだけは しない人だと
思ってたのに
（中鉢博士）黙れ！
Shut up!
（紅莉栖）キャッ
How dare you call it stealing?!
（中鉢博士）よくも盗むなどと
うっ ぐっ…
Why are you so smart?
なぜ お前は そんなに優秀なのだ？
A girl shouldn't be smarter than her father!
娘が親より優秀でいい
道理などない！
If it weren't for you, I would've been smart too!
お前さえいなければ
私は優秀でいられたのだ！
If it weren't for you...
お前さえいなければ…
（中鉢博士）ん？
（岡部）うわーっ
（紅莉栖）ゲホッ ゲホッ　はっ？
（中鉢博士）ええい
（岡部）ハア ハア…
You're that kid from earlier.
お前 さっきの…
So that's it?
そういうことか
You were plotting to ruin my conference together, huh?
貴様ら 示し合わせて―
私の会見を
台なしにしようとしていたんだな
フフッ フフフ　そうか
I see.
So that's it.
そういうことか…
Daddy!
パパ！
I'll protect her!
（岡部）守るんだ 紅莉栖を
How dare you insult me?
私を バカにするな！
（岡部）おっ うっ
うおっ
Why, you...
おのれ！
フフ フフフ…
Stop it, Daddy!
（紅莉栖）もうやめて パパ！
Please!
お願い…
Don't even speak to me!
私に… 指図するな！
Oh, shit!
（岡部）しまった！
あっ ぐっ
ぬおおおー
貴様に 何が分かる
私の気持ちが…
What do you know?
You don't know how I feel.
私の この屈辱が… 地獄が…
You don't know how I've been humiliated
and the shit I've been through!
パパ
If it weren't for you...
（中鉢博士）
お前さえいなければ…
（岡部）やめろ
Don't...
If it weren't for you...
（中鉢博士）
お前さえいなければ…
（紅莉栖）ぐぐ…
Don't do it!
（岡部）やめろー
（紅莉栖）パパ！
Kurisu...
（岡部）紅莉栖…
（紅莉栖）あっ…
かっ… は…
K-Kurisu!
（岡部）く… 紅莉栖
ハ… ハハハ
バカどもが…
Fools.
This is the perfect end for you.
お前らには ふさわしい末路だ
ハハハハ…
I'm sorry for getting you involved.
（紅莉栖）ごめんなさい…
巻き込んじゃって
Why?
（岡部）どうして…
Because he's my dad,
（紅莉栖）父親だから
パパに認められたくて…
I wanted him to accept me.
That's all.
それだけで…
Kurisu...
紅莉栖…
I'm scared...
（紅莉栖）怖いよ…
I... I don't want to die.
私… 死にたくない…
I don't want to die.
死にたくないよ
死に… たく…
I don't...
Kurisu...
（岡部）紅莉栖…
Kurisu!
紅莉栖！
あ… ああ…
うわあああー！
（まゆり）あっ
（橋田）ん？
They're back already!
（まゆり）もう戻ってきた
Okarin!
オカリーン
ハッ
うっ オカリン その血
Okarin, that blood...
（岡部）殺した…
It's all right.
大丈夫 これは
おじさんの血じゃないから
It's not his.
I was the one who killed Kurisu.
俺が…
俺が紅莉栖を殺した
I was the one who killed Kurisu.
俺が紅莉栖を殺した…
（まゆり）オカリン
Okarin?
I know it hurts, but you can't give up yet.
おじさん つらいだろうけど
まだ あきらめちゃダメ
We have enough fuel to go back one more time.
もう一度 過去に戻るだけの
燃料は残っている…
Shut up!
（岡部）うるさいっ！
Nothing will change!
どうせ また行っても同じだ
The attractor field convergence will kill her all over again.
アトラクタフィールドの
収束によって―
紅莉栖は死んでしまうんだ
It's your phone.
オカリンの携帯だ
A message?
（橋田）あ… メール？
（鈴羽）開けて
Open it.
But...
（まゆり）でも
（鈴羽）いいから
Just do it.
Turn on the TV.
Turn on the TV?
（まゆり）“テレビを見ろ”
Turn on the TV.
The TV?
テレビ？
Professor Nakabachi Defects to Russia
Mysterious Fire in Cargo Bay
The plane carrying Professor Nakabachi
made it to Russia,
（アナウンサー）
中鉢博士を乗せた飛行機は
貨物室に火災を起こしながらも
despite a mysterious cargo bay fire.
かろうじて亡命先のロシアに
着陸した模様です
We were very fortunate.
（中鉢博士）
それにしても助かったよ
If this hadn't triggered the metal detector,
これが金属探知機に
かかったおかげで―
Mayushii
the paper would've gone up.
論文が焼けずに済んだのだ
あー まゆしぃのメタルうーぱ
What's this?
That's Mayushii's metal Upa!
Look. It has Mayushii's name on it!
ほら見て
ここに まゆしぃの
名前書いてあるもん
（橋田）ホントだ
でも なんでロシアに？
She's right.
But what's it doing in Russia?
That paper is the start of everything.
あの論文が すべての始まりなんだ
（まゆり･橋田）ほえ？
Next comes the international time machine arms race.
（鈴羽）これをきっかけに―
大国間で しれつな
タイムマシン開発競争が始まる
To rule time is to rule the world.
時間を制することは
世界を制するも同じだからね
And that begins a world war.
そして 世界大戦に発展する
（まゆり･橋田）うわー
5.7 billion lives are at stake.
（鈴羽）
57億人の命が懸かってるの
Save Makise Kurisu and change this world line!
牧瀬紅莉栖を救って
世界線を変えて
It's impossible.
無理だよ
It's just like with Mayuri.
まゆりのときと同じなんだよ
No matter what I do, it'll end up the same.
どんなに あがこうが
結果は変わらない
Kurisu will die.
紅莉栖は死ぬんだ
How can you say that after only one time?
どうして
たった１回の失敗で
（岡部）１回？
One time?!
It's more than that.
バカ言うな 俺が何回…
How many times...
How many times do you think I've failed?!
何十回 失敗したと
思ってる！
I already know
俺には分かってるんだ
how insane this time loop is
この時間の輪が―
どれだけ不条理に
できているか
and what a cruel fate it has in store.
どれだけ残酷な結末を
用意しているか
I knew this...
分かっていた…
分かっていたんだ こうなるって…
I knew this would happen.
もう疲れた 疲れたよ
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
You're not the kind of person to quit halfway.
（まゆり）オカリンは途中で
あきらめる人じゃないよ
Mayushii knows this!
まゆしぃは知ってるもん
You're not the kind of person to ever give up.
オカリンは絶対
あきらめる人じゃない
Even when Mayushii couldn't say goodbye to her grandmother,
まゆしぃが おばあちゃんと
サヨナラできずにいたときも―
you never stopped going to her grave.
あきらめないで
毎日 お墓に来てくれた
That's why I could say goodbye.
だから
サヨナラできたんだよ
だから まゆしぃは
元気になったんだよ
That's why I got better!
（岡部）ハッ
So don't give up.
だから
あきらめちゃダメだよ
You should've received a video file on July 28th.
７月28日に
ムービーメールが来ていたはず
July 28th...
（岡部）７月28日…
You should be able to watch it
（鈴羽）今なら見れるはず
now that you've failed once to rescue Makise Kurisu.
（鈴羽）牧瀬紅莉栖の救出に
一度失敗した 今なら
どういうことだ
What do you mean?
I'm sorry I lied to you.
だまして ごめん
The plan called for you to fail once.
一度失敗するのは
計画の内だったんだ
So that you would see this.
おじさんが それを見るための…
What is this?
（岡部）これは…
（まゆり）んんー
Nice to meet you, me from 15 years ago.
（未来の岡部）
はじめましてだな　15年前の俺
（橋田･岡部）うっ
It's Okarin!
オカリンだ
If you've opened this message,
（未来の岡部）このメールを
開いているということは
then you've failed to rescue Kurisu.
紅莉栖を救うことに
失敗したということだな
さぞ つらかっただろう
It must've been painful,
but that pain gave rise to my obsession,
だが そのつらさが
俺に執念を与えた
so it had to happen.
だから なかったことにする
わけには いかなかったのだ
You could say it was a part of the preparation.
いわば 下ごしらえの
ようなものだな
Now we can begin the plan in earnest,
これで やっと計画の本題に
入ることができる
the plan to save Makise Kurisu
牧瀬紅莉栖を救い
シュタインズ･ゲートに入る計画だ
and enter Steins Gate.
We have two objectives.
条件は２つ
First, we must destroy the paper on time machines,
中鉢博士がロシアに持ち込んだ―
タイムマインに関する論文を
この世から葬り去ること
which Professor Nakabachi took to Russia.
Second, we must save Makise Kurisu.
もう１つは
牧瀬紅莉栖を救うことだ
If I could do that...
それが できれば…
But avoiding her death and changing the past are impossible
（未来の岡部）
だが 牧瀬紅莉栖の死を回避し
過去を改変するのは
because of the attractor field convergence.
アトラクタフィールドの
収束により不可能
Isn't that right?
そうだな？
I'll do my best to explain.
はっきり言おう
紅莉栖を救うことは可能だ
Saving Makise Kurisu is possible.
You're just approaching it the wrong way.
方法が間違っているだけなのだ
Listen well.
いいか よく聞け
You must not change the past once it's been established.
確定した過去を変えてはいけない
You must not undo what you saw that day.
最初の お前自身が見たことを
なかったことにしてはならない
If you do either, the past will change, and all will be lost.
なかったことにすれば
過去改変が起こり
すべてが失われる
Remember your experiences in the alpha world line.
お前がアルファ世界線で
経験したことを思い出せ
It was only three weeks,
わずか３週間だったが―
but you should have memories of your time with Makise Kurisu,
お前には 牧瀬紅莉栖と
過ごした記憶があるはずだ
everyone's sacrifices to save Mayuri,
紅莉栖と共に まゆりを救うため
多くの思いを犠牲にし…
and everything that's happened.
もがき続けた経験が
存在しているはずだ
You must not waste those three weeks.
お前の３週間の世界線漂流を
ムダにしてはならない
なかったことにしては いけない
You must not undo them.
The only reason you wish so desperately to save her
いくつもの世界線を
旅してきたからこそ
is because of the world lines you experienced.
紅莉栖を助けたいと思う
お前は そこにいる
And it's the sole reason
タイムマシン開発に すべてを
ささげた俺がここにいる
I devoted my life to developing a time machine.
お前が立っている その場所は―
The reason you've managed to get
俺たちが 紅莉栖を助けたいと
願ったからこそ―
as far as you have is that we both want to save Kurisu.
到達できた場所なんだ
Thus, you must deceive your other self.
だから だませ
お前自身を
紅莉栖が死んだという
過去を変えずに 彼女を救え
Save her without changing the past where she died.
Make your past self
生きている紅莉栖を
過去の自分に死んだと観測させろ
mistake a living Kurisu for a dead one.
If you do, the past won't change.
そうすれば 過去改変は起きない
I get it.
（岡部）そうか…
What does he mean?
（まゆり）どういうこと？
Okarin, do you know?
（橋田）オカリン 分かるん？
I know you'll understand me.
（未来の岡部）
お前なら分かるはずだ
By the way, the time machine's ID is C204.
ちなみにタイムマシンの形式は
Ｃ２０４型
I'm sure you know what that stands for.
頭文字が何を意味するか
言うまでもないな？
Christina...
クリスティーナ
（未来の岡部）
そして 目的の世界線を
And I was the one who named the target world line Steins Gate.
シュタインズ･ゲートと
名付けたのも俺だ
You know why I named it that.
なぜ その名なのかも
お前なら分かるはずだ
It doesn't really mean anything.
（岡部･未来の岡部）
特に意味はない
Isn't that right?
（未来の岡部）そうだろ？
これより 最終ミッション―
I will now explain the parameters
of the final mission, Operation Skuld.
オペレーションスクルドの
概要を説明する
Change the result without changing the established past.
確定した過去を変えずに
結果を変えろ
The past consists of Makise Kurisu lying in a pool of blood,
kako wa hanareteyuki mirai wa chikazukuno?
The past retreats, but does the future truly approach?
and Okabe Rintarou seeing her there.
Change the past without changing that.
kansokusha wa itsuka mujun ni kizuku
An observer would realize the contradictions there
Deceive your other self.
Deceive the world.
kami no tsukuridashita sekai wa kanzennaru mono de zettai no kinkou
This world shaped by God is perfect and lies in absolute balance
That is what you must do to reach Steins Gate.
Good luck.
El Psy Congroo.
sore wa orikasanaru guuzen uchuu kibo no kiseki
A superimposed coincidence, a miracle on a cosmic scale
What was that?
mamoraretekita GATE "kisei" wa owatta
The restrictions on the guarded gate are now abolished
Was that you, 15 years from now?
血まみれで倒れている
牧瀬紅莉栖と―
The voice was so deep!
それを見た 岡部倫太郎
Open the Eyes
"zero" ga kako de "ichi" ga mirai "ima" wa dokonimo nai
"Zero" is the past and "One" is the future, "The Present" is a fabrication
その確定した過去を変えずに
結果を変えるのだ
最初のお前をだませ
somuku koto no dekinu LOGIC
This is an undeniable logic
Operation Skuld?
世界をだませ
El Psy Congroo?
それがシュタインズ･ゲートに
到達するための条件だ
Open the Eyes
I still talk like that when I'm 33 years old?
heikousuru musuu no sen sentaku wa boutoku e
Amidst the countless parallel lines, I choose blasphemy
I sound like a nerdy teen.
健闘を祈る
bokura no "sonzai" sae utagau sono me ni utsuru keshiki wa
Doubting existence itself, Those Eyes bear witness to
エル･プサイ･コングルゥ
Okarin?
I'll do it,
いったい 何なん？
if that is the choice of Steins Gate.
"shuusoku" o suru
Convergence
今のが15年後のオカリン？
I am the mad scientist, Hououin Kyouma!
声 渋かったよね
（岡部）クククッ
Deceiving the world is nothing to me!
フハハハッ
オペレーションスクルドだと？
He's back to the usual Okarin.
エル･プサイ･コングルゥだと？
Still, Mayushii likes Okarin better when he's like this.
33にもなって
何をやっているんだ俺は
futatsu no hari ga sasu jikan no gainen mo
Even the basic concept of time, as depicted by two hands of a clock
I'll say it once more.
まるで 厨二病(ちゅうにびょう)全開じゃないか
kansokusha shidai de hizumi o miseru
Will bend and distort to the choice of the Observer
I am...
the mad scientist...
（まゆり）オカリン
（岡部）やってやる
kami ni ataerareta eichi wa kanarazu "hate" ga aru zettai no ryouiki
The knowledge God gifted us must have some limit, an absolute territory
Hououin Kyouma...
それがシュタインズ･ゲートの
選択というのならばな！
and the world is in the palm of my hand!
俺は狂気のマッドサイエンティスト
鳳凰院凶真(ほうおういんきょうま)！
Sore wa oroka yue no guuzen manekarezaru kiseki
It tells us that these are foolish notions and unwanted miracles
世界をだますなど造作もない！
フー ハハハハハッ
Tozasaretekita gate "kisei" wa owatta
The gate that once was shut is supervised no more
おおっ いつものオカリンに戻った
でもね まゆしぃは こっちの
オカリンのほうが好きなのです
Open the eyes
Kousoku he to te wo nobashita omoide no parusu ga
My mind wished to reach the speed of light
あえて もう一度言おう
この俺は…
Tobikomu fukashigi na logic
and fell into an eldritch logic
狂気のマッドサイエンティスト
鳳凰院凶真！
Open the eyes
Uchuu ga mada kakushimotta chitsujo no nai riron
The lawless rules of the universe remain hidden from us
世界は この俺の
手の中にある！
Mugen to yobareta ten to ten ga fusei na chikara wo karite
What we call eternity is but dots connected, empowering each other
"Saisei" wo suru
and resurrecting us time and time again
～